(Sheldon:)Amy, don't you agree we should
leave now and get in line?
(Amy:)Actually, as the newest member
of your social group,
(Amy:)I believe I'll gain more
acceptance by arbitrarily
(Amy:)siding with your friends
from time to time.
(Sheldon:)Shrewd.
(Amy:)Leonard, you're right.
(Amy:)We should enjoy our meal,
arrive late,
(Amy:)and risk winding up
with terrible seats,
(Amy:)assuming we get in at all.
(Leonard:)Thank you, Amy.
(Amy:)See? It's working.
(Bernadette:)Knock-knock.
(Howard:)Who's there?
(Bernadette:)Olive.
(Howard:)Olive you, too.
(Leonard:)Guys, that's really
starting to get old.
(Bernadette:)Knock-knock.
(Howard:)Who's there?
(Howard:)I have a girlfriend
and you don't.
(Leonard:)Hysterical!
(Sheldon:)Wait, now, we don't know
that yet. He isn't finished.
I have a girlfriend
and you don't who?
So. Are you sure you don't want
to come with us to Raiders?
(Bernadette:)Oh, no. That movie
has melting faces.
(Bernadette:)It reminds me
too much of the time
(Bernadette:)I dropped that vial of
flesh-eating bacteria